Guide to the Karl Ichiro Akiya Papers TAM.236
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Artwork and Photographs, 1942-1990
  - Artwork: Drawings, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Artwork: Hiroshima and Nagasaki Children's Drawings (reproductions), 1945-1950 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Artwork: Kwansei Gakuin University (Kansei Gakuin Daigaku) Campus (drawings), undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Artwork: Kwansei Gakuin University (Kansei Gakuin Daigaku) (postcards), undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Artwork: Nisei Progressives – 15 Japanese Woodcuts, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Artwork: Postcards, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Artwork: Untitled Artwork, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Artwork: Washington School of Art Assignments (drawings), undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Photos: Kwansei Gakuin University (Kansei Gakuin Daigaku) Campus (slides), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Photos: Kwansei Gakuin University (Kansei Gakuin Daigaku) Alumni Club New Year's Party (negatives), 1990 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Photos: Photo Album (color photocopy), 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Series V: Oversize and Ephemera, 1949-1987
  - Bank of Tokyo Certificate of Appreciation, Sep 15, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Broken Glass and Rock from Peekskill Riots, Aug 27, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - * Identification Cards, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Kwansei Gakuin Junior High School: Plaque, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Kwansei Gakuin University: Alumni Association Banner, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Kwansei Gakuin University: Commemorative Spoons, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Kwansei Gakuin University: Keychain, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Lifetime Achievement Award Plaque, Jan 14, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Paint Brushes, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Videos: Seventy Years of the Japanese Communist Party (VHS, Japanese Language), 1992 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Videos: Pearl Harbor (Beta), undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Videos: Topaz (VHS), undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Wallet, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Roger Hargrave Spanish Civil War Scrapbook, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Kwansei Gakuin University: Appreciation Certificate, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 3)
  - Kwansei Gakuin University: Banner, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Bank of Tokyo Annual Outing, 1959-1966 (Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Photos: Bank of Tokyo Annual Christmas Party, 1959-1976 (Box Shared Tamiment 069, Folder 13)
  - Mixed Materials: original art by H. Sugimoto, R. Tanaka, M. Okubo, others; photo exhibit of Hiroshima and Nagasaki aftermath; calligraphy on wood boards; vinyl LPs, undated (Box 12)
  - 100th Anniversary poster, Kwansei Gakuin University, 1989 (Flat-file-folder 1)